[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Dinosaurs can be divided into two groups: Ornithschians and Saurischians. The difference between them is mainly in the structure of this part of their bodies.", "correct_answer": "Hips", "incorrect_answers": ["Eyes", "Teeth", "Toes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is a major US airline and a subsidiary of Delta Air Lines?", "correct_answer": "Northwest Airlines", "incorrect_answers": ["Southwest Airlines", "Northeast Airlines", "Southeast Airlines"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mr. A  picks three cards from a 52-card deck. Mr. B rolls a pair of dice once. Mr. C rolls three dice. Mr. A must pick three aces. Mr. B must roll a 13. Mr. C must roll a  two. Who has the best odds?", "correct_answer": "Mr. A", "incorrect_answers": ["The odds are equal", "Mr. C.", "Mr. B"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Your friends favorite breakfast is a shingle with shimmy and shake, squeeze one.   What does he like to eat for breakfast?", "correct_answer": "Buttered toast with jam and orange juice", "incorrect_answers": ["French toast and apple juice", "Link sausage,  toast and juice", "Short stack of pancakes and instant coffee"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Scarface, this actress played Tonys love interest who later becomes his wife.", "correct_answer": "Michelle Pfeiffer", "incorrect_answers": ["Michelle Cruz", "Madonna", "Eva Longoria"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the symbol for Gold?", "correct_answer": "Au", "incorrect_answers": ["Ao", "G", "Gd"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pommes de terre is a French term literally translated as apples of the earth.  In English the term refers to which of the following?", "correct_answer": "potatoes", "incorrect_answers": ["tomatoes", "apples", "beets"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these actors has played both a disruptive student and an inspiring teacher?", "correct_answer": "Sidney Poitier", "incorrect_answers": ["Richard Harris", "Sean Connery", "Hugh Grant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these penguin species is the closest relative of the Magellanic Penguin?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["African Penguin", "Galapagos Penguin", "Humboldt Penguin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of the following is indicative of Direct Disc Labeling capabilities?", "correct_answer": "LightScribe", "incorrect_answers": ["SATA 3.0Gb/s", "Sharpie enabled", "DL DVD\u00b1RW/CD-RW"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "300 lbs of blood were used in the last scene of this 1992 Peter Jackson film.", "correct_answer": "Dead Alive", "incorrect_answers": ["The Necro Files", "Killing Birds", "Bad Taste"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which country is Richard\u2019s wife Susan shot in the 2006 movie Babel?", "correct_answer": "Morocco", "incorrect_answers": ["Mexico", "Egypt", "Guatemala"]}]